Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
- Football, 1895-2007; 1895 2007; In 1892, the first official football game at NC State was played against a local prep school, Raleigh Male Academy; in 1893, State played their first intercollegiate game against Tennessee. The 1895 team was the first to wear the now traditional red and white colore
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 6 Nov. 1948 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Duquesne: program, 13 Nov. 1948 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. Villanova: program, 27 Nov. 1948 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Football press releases, 1949 (Legalbox 104, Folder 12)
  - Media guide, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Statistics, 1949 (Legalbox 104, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 24 Sept. 1949 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 15 Oct. 1949 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Polytechnic Institute: program, 29 Oct. 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. University of Richmond: program, 5 Nov. 1949 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Football press releases, 1950 (Legalbox 175, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1950 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, 1950 (Legalbox 175, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Catawba: program, 30 Sept. 1950 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 14 Oct. 1950 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Polytechnic Institute: program, 28 Oct. 1950 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 18 Nov. 1950 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Football press releases, 1951 (Legalbox 175, Folder 4)
  - Media guide, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Statistics, 1951 (Legalbox 175, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Catawba: program, 15 Sept. 1951 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 29 Sept. 1951 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 13 Oct. 1951 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Football press releases, 1952 (Legalbox 175, Folder 6)
  - Media guide, 1952 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Statistics, 1952 (Legalbox 175, Folder 7)
  - Red-White spring football game, 2 May 1952 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. George Washington: program, 27 Sept. 1952 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Davidson: program, 11 Oct. 1952 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 18 Oct. 1952 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: program, 25 Oct. 1952 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference football records form, 1953 (Legalbox 175, Folder 8)
  - Football press releases, 1953 (Legalbox 175, Folder 9)
  - Media guide, 1953 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Statistics, 1953 (Legalbox 175, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Davidson: program, 10 Oct. 1953 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - NC State vs. William and Mary: program, 31 Oct. 1953 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: program, 28 Nov. 1953 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Media guide, 1954 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Statistics, 1954 (Legalbox 175, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: program, 18 Sept. 1954 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 23 Oct. 1954 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - NC State vs. Furman: program, 30 Oct. 1954 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Football press releases: player features, 1955 (Legalbox 175, Folder 12)
  - Freshman Football: general information, 1955 (Legalbox 175, Folder 13)
  - Media guide, 1955 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Pre-season football press releases, 1955 (Legalbox 175, Folder 14)
  - Questionnaires, 1955 (Legalbox 175, Folder 15)
  - Statistics, 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. William and Mary: game information, 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Boston University: game information, 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: game information, 17 Sept. 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: program, 17 Sept. 1955 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 24 Sept. 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 24 Sept. 1955 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 1 Oct. 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 1 Oct. 1955 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 15 Oct. 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 15 Oct. 1955 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Villanova: game information, 22 Oct. 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Villanova: program, 22 Oct. 1955 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Furman: game information, 29 Oct. 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Furman: program, 29 Oct. 1955 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: game information, 12 Nov. 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Coal Bowl): program, 12 Nov. 1955 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. West Virginia: game information, 25 Nov. 1955 (Legalbox 176, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. West Virginia: program, 25 Nov. 1955 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1956 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Commentary for football film clip, 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 12)
  - Football press releases, 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 13)
  - Freshman Football questionnaires, 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 14)
  - Media guide, 1956 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Pre-season football press releases, schedule, 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 15)
  - Rosters, 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 16)
  - Rosters, 1956-1970 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Statistics, 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 22 Sept. 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 22 Sept. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: game information, 29 Sept. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Good Neighbor Bowl): program, 29 Sept. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 6 Oct. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: program, 6 Oct. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: game information, 13 Oct. 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 19)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: program, 13 Oct. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Dayton: game information, 20 Oct. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. University of Dayton: program, 20 Oct. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 27 Oct. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 27 Oct. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 3 Nov. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 10 Nov. 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 20)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 10 Nov. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: game information, 17 Nov. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - NC State vs. Penn State: program, 17 Nov. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 22 Nov. 1956 (Legalbox 176, Folder 21)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 22 Nov. 1956 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Clippings, 1957 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Football press releases, 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Football questionnaires, 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1957 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Pre-season football press releases, 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 3)
  - Press, radio, TV, 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 4)
  - Rosters, 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 21 Sept. 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 21 Sept. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 28 Sept. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 28 Sept. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 5 Oct. 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: program, 5 Oct. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: game information, 12 Oct. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: program, 12 Oct. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Miami: game information, 18 Oct. 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Miami: program, 18 Oct. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 26 Oct. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 26 Oct. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 2 Nov. 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 2 Nov. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. William and Mary: game information, 9 Nov. 1957 (Legalbox 177, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. William and Mary: program, 9 Nov. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: game information, 16 Nov. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 23 Nov. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 23 Nov. 1957 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Football press releases, 1958 (Legalbox 177, Folder 12)
  - Freshman Football questionnaires, 1958 (Legalbox 177, Folder 13)
  - Media guide, 1958 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Pre-season football press releases, 1958 (Legalbox 177, Folder 14)
  - Rosters, 1958 (Legalbox 177, Folder 15)
  - Spring football prospectus, 1958 (Legalbox 177, Folder 16)
  - Statistics, 1958 (Legalbox 178, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 20 Sept. 1958 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 27 Sept. 1958 (Legalbox 178, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 4 Oct. 1958 (Legalbox 178, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 4 Oct. 1958 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 11 Oct. 1958 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 11 Oct. 1958 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - NC State vs. William and Mary: game information, 18 Oct. 1958 (Legalbox 178, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. William and Mary: program, 18 Oct. 1958 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 25 Oct. 1958 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 25 Oct. 1958 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: game information, 1 Nov. 1958 (Legalbox 178, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi Southern: game information, 8 Nov. 1958 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 15 Nov. 1958 (Legalbox 178, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 22 Nov. 1958 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 22 Nov. 1958 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Football press releases, Sept. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 7)
  - Football press releases, Oct. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 8)
  - Football press releases, Nov. - Dec. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 9)
  - Football press releases: player features, 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Football questionnaires, 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 11)
  - Media guide, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Pre-season Football press releases, 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 12)
  - Press, radio, TV, 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 13)
  - Roster, 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 14)
  - Schedule, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Spring Football prospectus, 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 15)
  - Statistics, 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 16)
  - Varsity-Old Timers football game, 21 Mar. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: game information, 19 Sept. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 3 Oct. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 3 Oct. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 10 Oct. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: program, 10 Oct. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 17 Oct. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 19)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 24 Oct. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 20)
  - NC State vs. Wyoming: game information, 31 Oct. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 21)
  - NC State vs. Wyoming: program, 31 Oct. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi Southern: game information, 7 Nov. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi Southern: program, 7 Nov. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. UCLA: game information, 13 Nov. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 22)
  - NC State vs. UCLA: program, 13 Nov. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 21 Nov. 1959 (Legalbox 178, Folder 23)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 21 Nov. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 5 Dec. 1959 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - All-Star honors, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 1)
  - Attendance, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 2)
  - Football press releases: player features, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 3)
  - Football Writers' Association of America, 1960-1961 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Freshman Football general information, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Football questionnaire, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 5)
  - "Hometown" Football press releases, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 6)
  - "Look" All-America Team, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 7)
  - Media guide, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Pre-season clippings, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 8)
  - Pre-season Football press releases, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 9)
  - Radio, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 10)
  - Roster, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 11)
  - Schedule, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 12)
  - Spring Football prospectus, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 13)
  - Statistics, 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 14)
  - Red-White game, 26 Mar. 1960 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: game information, 17 Sept. 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: program, 17 Sept. 1960 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 24 Sept. 1960 (Legalbox 179, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 24 Sept. 1960 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 1 Oct. 1960 (Legalbox 180, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 1 Oct. 1960 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 8 Oct. 1960 (Legalbox 180, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 8 Oct. 1960 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 15 Oct. 1960 (Legalbox 180, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 15 Oct. 1960 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi Southern: game information, 22 Oct. 1960 (Legalbox 180, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi Southern: program, 22 Oct. 1960 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - NC State vs. UCLA: game information, 29 Oct. 1960 (Legalbox 180, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. UCLA: program, 29 Oct. 1960 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 5 Nov. 1960 (Legalbox 180, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 5 Nov. 1960 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Arizona State: game information, 12 Nov. 1960 (Legalbox 180, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Arizona State: program, 12 Nov. 1960 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 19 Nov. 1960 (Legalbox 180, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 19 Nov. 1960 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Senior Bowl (12th Annual), 7 Jan. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - All-Star honors, 1961 (Legalbox 180, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference records, 1961 (Legalbox 180, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Coaches' clinic, 1961 (Legalbox 180, Folder 11)
  - Florida Citrus Commission experiment, 1961-1963 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Football general information, 1961 (Legalbox 180, Folder 12)
  - Freshman Football questionnaires, 1961 (Legalbox 180, Folder 13)
  - Media guide, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Pre-season Football press releases, 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 1)
  - Rosters, 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 3)
  - Ticket application, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Wolfpack Radio Network, 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 4)
  - Red-White football game, 25 Mar. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 7 Sept. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Wyoming: game information, 23 Sept. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Wyoming: program, 23 Sept. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 30 Sept. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 30 Sept. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 7 Oct. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Alabama: game information, 14 Oct. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Alabama: program, 14 Oct. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 21 Oct. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 21 Oct. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 28 Oct. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 28 Oct. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi Southern: game information, 4 Nov. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi Southern: program, 4 Nov. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 11 Nov. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 11 Nov. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 18 Nov. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 18 Nov. 1961 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 25 Nov. 1961 (Legalbox 181, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: program, 25 Nov. 1961 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Shrine East-West All-Star Football Game (37th Annual): program, 30 Dec. 1961 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - All-Star honors, 1962 (Legalbox 181, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1962 (Legalbox 181, Folder 17)
  - Coaches' clinic, 1962 (Legalbox 181, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Football clippings, 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Football general information, 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Football questionnaires, 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 3)
  - General information, 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 4)
  - Greenville (South Carolina) Touchdown Club, 1962-1969 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Media guide, 1962 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame, 1962-1969 (Legalbox 182, Folder 5)
  - Player features, 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 6)
  - Pre-season Football press releases, 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 7)
  - Spring Football, 24 Feb. - 31 Mar. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 8)
  - Statistics, 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 9)
  - Red-White game, 31 Mar. 1962 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Red-White game, 31 Mar. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 10)
  - East-West Coaches All-America game, 29 Jun. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 11)
  - College All-Star game, 3 Aug. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 22 Sept. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 22 Sept. 1962 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 29 Sept. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: program, 29 Sept. 1962 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 6 Oct. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 6 Oct. 1962 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Nebraska: game information, 13 Oct. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. Nebraska: program, 13 Oct. 1962 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi Southern: game information, 20 Oct. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 27 Oct. 1962 (Legalbox 182, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 27 Oct. 1962 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Georgia: game information, 3 Nov. 1962 (Legalbox 183, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Georgia: program, 3 Nov. 1962 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 10 Nov. 1962 (Legalbox 183, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 10 Nov. 1962 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 17 Nov. 1962 (Legalbox 183, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: program, 17 Nov. 1962 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 22 Nov. 1962 (Legalbox 183, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Football clippings, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Football general information, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Football questionnaires, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 7)
  - General information, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 8)
  - Honors, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 9)
  - Media guide, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Player features, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 10)
  - Pre-season general information, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 11)
  - Spring football, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 12)
  - Statistics, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 13)
  - Ticket order form, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Varsity Football clippings, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 14)
  - Red-White game, 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 21 Sept. 1963 (Legalbox 183, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: program, 21 Sept. 1963 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. Southern Mississippi: game information, 28 Sept. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Southern Mississippi: program, 28 Sept. 1963 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 5 Oct. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: program, 5 Oct. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: game information, 12 Oct. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina: program, 12 Oct. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 19 Oct. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 19 Oct. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Duke: game information, 26 Oct. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 26 Oct. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Virginia: game information, 2 Nov. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Virginia (Civitan Bowl: 6th Annual): program, 2 Nov. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: game information, 9 Nov. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech: program, 9 Nov. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: game information, 16 Nov. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Florida State: program, 16 Nov. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: game information, 22 Nov. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: program, 22 Nov. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi State (Liberty Bowl): game information, 21 Dec. 1963 (Legalbox 184, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi State (5th Annual Liberty Bowl): media guide, 21 Dec. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Mississippi State (5th Annual Liberty Bowl): program, 21 Dec. 1963 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - All-Star honors, 1964 (Legalbox 184, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1964 (Legalbox 184, Folder 12)
  - Freshman Football clippings, 1964 (Legalbox 184, Folder 13)
  - Freshman Football general information, 1964 (Legalbox 185, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Football questionnaires, 1964 (Legalbox 185, Folder 2)
  - General information, 1964 (Legalbox 185, Folder 3)
  - Media guide, 1964 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Ticket application form, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Player features, 1964 (Legalbox 185, Folder 4)
  - Spring Football, 1964 (Legalbox 185, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, 1964 (Legalbox 185, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: game information, 14 Sept. 1964 (Legalbox 185, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill: program, 19 Sept. 1964 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: game information, 26 Sept. 1964 (Legalbox 185, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Clemson: program, 26 Sept. 1964 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Maryland: game information, 3 Oct. 1964 (Legalbox 185, Folder 9)